[{"answer": " Hi, Kim.  Hows everything going", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Oh, just OK", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Hi, Kim.  Hows everything going", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Is there something wrong", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Oh, just OK", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Well, Im just feeling a little lonely and homesick.  Im still getting adjusted to lif", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Is there something wrong", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " How long have you been here now", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Well, Im just feeling a little lonely and homesick.  Im still getting adjusted to lif", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Two months", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 23, "question": " How long have you been here now", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Thats such a short time.  Im sure its normal for everyone to feel homesick fo", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Two months", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Yeah, I guess so", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Thats such a short time.  Im sure its normal for everyone to feel homesick fo", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Do you talk to your family and friends back home much", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Yeah, I guess so", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " I talk to my parents about once a week and to my friends every couple of weeks", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Do you talk to your family and friends back home much", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Do you call them", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 34, "question": " I talk to my parents about once a week and to my friends every couple of weeks", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " I dont have a landline.  So, I use my cell phone to call my parents", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Do you call them", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Isnt it expensive to use your cell phone to call long distance", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 36, "question": " I dont have a landline.  So, I use my cell phone to call my parents", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " If I just used my cell phone it would be.  But, I buy pre-paid phone cards and us", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Isnt it expensive to use your cell phone to call long distance", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Is it expensive", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 41, "question": " If I just used my cell phone it would be.  But, I buy pre-paid phone cards and us", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " No.  Its about seven cents a minute", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Is it expensive", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Oh, thats not bad at all", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 43, "question": " No.  Its about seven cents a minute", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Do you talk to your parents a lot", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Oh, thats not bad at all", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " I guess I talk to them about once every two weeks.  They live on the other side o", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Do you talk to your parents a lot", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Is it expensive to call them", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 49, "question": " I guess I talk to them about once every two weeks.  They live on the other side o", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Well, they usually call me, but sometimes I make a collect call to talk to them, s", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Is it expensive to call them", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Oh, youre a bad daughter!  Just kidding", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Well, they usually call me, but sometimes I make a collect call to talk to them, s", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " What about your friends?  Do you call them often", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Oh, youre a bad daughter!  Just kidding", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " We dont usually talk on the phone.  Usually I just email them, or we talk onlin", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 56, "question": " What about your friends?  Do you call them often", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Ive never heard of VoIPs.  How do they work", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 60, "question": " We dont usually talk on the phone.  Usually I just email them, or we talk onlin", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Its very simple.  Both people have to download a companys free software.  The", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Ive never heard of VoIPs.  How do they work", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Thats so cool!  So, you can call anywhere in the world for free", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Its very simple.  Both people have to download a companys free software.  The", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Yep.  Its the cheapest way for my friends and I to stay in touch", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Thats so cool!  So, you can call anywhere in the world for free", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Ill have to try it out.  Will you show me one day", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Yep.  Its the cheapest way for my friends and I to stay in touch", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Ill have to try it out.  Will you show me one day", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Well, Im sorry that youre missing your friends and family.  It must be hard bein", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Thanks", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Well, Im sorry that youre missing your friends and family.  It must be hard bein", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Would you like to go see a movie with me tomorrow?  It might cheer you up", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Thanks", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " That would be great, thank you", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Would you like to go see a movie with me tomorrow?  It might cheer you up", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Sure.  Ill check whats playing and we can talk about it tomorrow", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 79, "question": " That would be great, thank you", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Sounds good", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Sure.  Ill check whats playing and we can talk about it tomorrow", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " OK, see you tomorrow", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Sounds good", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "02-03", "aSentId": 82, "question": " OK, see you tomorrow", "qSentId": 81}]
